Our Secret
EP01
Please take a look at our press.
Thank you.
Hey, you there.
This is the boy's dormitory.
You can't get in.
I know. I am a freshman.
I just need to go inside to look for someone.
That's not OK. You can't go against the rule.
Just give me two minutes.
What's the matter with you, kid?
Just two minutes.
No.
If you keep doing this, I have to call the security office.
Zhou Siyue.
Zhou Siyue, I am coming for you now!
Zhou Siyue, come out now!
If you don't come out, I'll go in.
Zhou Siyue.
Zhou Siyue, I am coming to you now.
Ding Xian.
Zhou Siyue.
I'm so glad to see you.
You don't answer my phone calls or messages.
I thought you wouldn't come out to see me.
I am here to tell you something.
Say it.
I like you.
Did you ever like me?
Ding Xian.
I have no intention to have a relationship with anyone.
It's late. You should go back.
Focus on your classes.
Don't come for me again.
We promised to go to Huaqing University together.
Now I've fulfilled my promise.
I just want to know,
have you ever liked me?
Does it really matter,
if I have or not?
Ding Xian.
We both have our own lives.
So what?
Zhou Siyue.
Do you know my secret?
It is late. I should leave now.
Activate.
August, 2009.
The summer in the south was really hot.
We said goodbye to Keshan Town
and moved to Shenhai.
Everything outside the window was new to me.
It was a new beginning.
I hoped Shenhai, this city,
could be friendly to me.
I wanted to maintain my good grades in the coming term.
I wanted to make new friends.
I hoped everything could go well.
Please be careful.
You need to be careful with this cabinet.
Come, this way.
Xian.
Your books, here you are.
Siyue.
The keys.
Why are you always so lazy?
What's wrong?
I sprained my ankle.
What are you doing here, standing?
Hurry up and move your things. Don't dawdle.
Ding Juncong.
So spacious.
Hurry up, guys.
We need to have a meal outside later.
Yes, the fridge, put it against the wall.
The rest can be put in the secondary bedroom.
Cong, Xian.
You two share one room.
- I refuse. - I refuse.
I've grown up
I don't want to live in the same room with him.
Or, I can live in school.
Live in school?
With such a good apartment, you want to waste money on that?
Do you think that we have too much money?
Fine. Fine.
There is still one small room left.
It doesn't need to be used as my study.
Make it a bedroom for them.
Is that OK, Wanxian?
OK. You two can choose by yourselves.
OK.
Slowly.
Then I want this room.
Me too.
Ding Juncong!
Why are you pushing me?
Mum!
What are you doing?
You!
Apologize.
No way.
Fine, if you don't apologize,
this room is mine.
No.
You are just a kid.
What do you want such a big room for?
Whatever I want!
I want this room!
Xian, you are the elder sister.
Just behave like one and let your brother have it, OK?
Mum.
Wanxian, where is my medical case?
I don't know.
Look for it by yourself.
You...
How did the medical case disappear?
Xian, are you alright?
I am fine.
If you are fine, hurry up then.
The Zhou family is waiting.
I don't want to go.
Don't dawdle. Hurry up.
Coming!
- Zhou. - Wencheng.
I've looked forward to your visit.
Please, come in.
Say hello to Uncle Zhou.
You don't have to change your shoes.
- Hello, Uncle Zhou. - Hello, Uncle Zhou.
You don't have to change them.
Better change them.
We don't want to stain your floor.
What is this about?
I have caused troubles for you about the school thing.
Just take these as a token of my gratitude.
Why are you being so formal with me now.
I will put these here.
Don't need to change your shoes. Just come in.
Xiaoyun.
Wencheng is here.
Hello.
So busy here, huh?
Ding, Wanxian, welcome.
This is
Auntie Li, whom I always mentioned to you guys.
Right?
Sorry, Auntie Li.
Actually my mum never mentioned you before.
I've always wanted to pay you a visit with Xian.
Right?
The first sign of the rebellious phase of adolescence,
lie without blinking.
Auntie Li, nice to meet you.
I have heard a lot about you from my mum.
Such a good girl.
Wencheng, have a seat.
Right, come in.
Please sit down and get ready for the meal.
OK. Change your shoes.
Your dad and Uncle Zhou have been friends since they were kids.
It's all for your Uncle Zhou's help that your dad can work in Shenhai.
Don't mess around, you two.
Before you come,
I told Xiaoyun that
- it's been too long since last time we met Wencheng. - Please sit.
We must have a good drink tonight.
Right? A good drink.
Hurry up.
You don't object, right?
Not at all.
You should drink some too.
OK, thanks.
They are Siyue's classmates.
They come to play games today.
Uncle, Auntie.
-Hello. -Where is Siyue?
He falls asleep again.
Get him out.
Childe Zhou, stop sleeping.
Your mum is asking you to come for meal!
Coming.
Study makes Children these days too tired.
So many people here.
Siyue,
say hello to your Uncle Ding and Auntie Ye.
Hello, Uncle Ding, Auntie Ye.
You have grown so much.
Sorry about him being late.
What to be sorry about? Come on.
It has been years since we last met.
Let's toast and celebrate.
Right, welcome, guys!
Thank you. Sorry for the troubles.
Thank you so much.
Help yourselves.
Xian, do you still remember?
This is Siyue. You two met when you were still kids.
Siyue,
a really handsome boy.
You have grown so much so quickly.
I hugged you when you were still a kid.
How time flies!
That's right.
They are in high school now.
Right, Xian.
I heard your rank was high in the senior high school entrance examination.
695.
That's great.
It wasn't that good.
Our Xian,
she was studying until two o'clock midnight.
And she won't listen to my persuasion.
She loves studying so much.
Siyue, how's your grade?
Me?
680.
But that barely reaches the minimum passing score.
Siyue is very talented.
He passed the line even though he took the exam casually.
Before the exam, we played video games together.
You are also Siyue's classmate, right?
What's your score?
Auntie.
No matter how the grade is,
if you pass, then it is enough.
The same as what I told Xian.
Enough is good enough.
But our Xian,
she loves studying so much and doesn't want to lose to anyone.
OK. Talk less and eat your meal.
I can tell that Xian is a good girl.
She will definitely achieve something in the future.
That's because you taught her well, Ding.
That's not my credit. You are joking.
I need to learn from you.
Learn from me?
We learn from each other.
Indeed. Regarding her study,
Xian never worries me.
Siyue,
if you get any problems about study,
you two can discuss them together.
Xianxian knows them well.
No problem, Auntie.
I will.
That's great.
You guys
should contact more from now on.
After all, your grandfathers
had a betrothal planned for you when you were still kids.
Why did you mention that?
But the topic goes there naturally.
That is really the case.
But it is too early for them
to talk about this.
After all, they are just high school students now.
Right.
They need to put study in the first place.
Come on.
What should I do to break off the betrothal?
You are such a kid. Your Auntie Ye is just joking.
And you take it seriously?
That's right.
I am joking along with Auntie Ye.
Come on.
What an interesting kid.
Who wants you?
Uncle Ding, Auntie Ye, please excuse me.
I am full already.
You eat so little?
I ate too much this morning. Please continue.
Me too. I am full now.
Me too.
Come on, ignore them.
Sorry about them.
The boys of this age are
kinda rebellious.
Right.
Same here, too.
Right, they are quite the same.
Sis, I need to go to the bathroom.
OK. I'll take you there.
I scored 695.
Our Xianxian is such a nice girl.
She doesn't need me to worry.
Our Xianxian knows everything.
Her mother wants to claim kinship with Siyue.
Who still makes child betrothal nowadays?
Right. So funny.
Did you see the bump on her head?
Didn't it look like a horn?
She tried to hide it from us, but we still can see it.
Like the monster Shrek.
That green one, right?
Who's his wife anyway?
Fiona.
Princess Fiona.
How do you feel?
Now that you have a fiancée,
how do you feel?
Can you cut the crap?
You dare to kick me again?
Sis, the toilet paper runs out.
No way. Do you think that she heard everything?
What should we do?
Open the door.
Fix the mistake you made. Hurry.
Monster...
Beauty, what can I help you with?
There is no toilet paper in the bathroom.
Do you have any?
Yes.
Toilet paper. Toilet paper.
You can't drink anymore.
No, can't drink anymore, Zhou.
Didn't you just hear everything?
You're good at drinking now.
If I break off the betrothal,
will you be happy?
Yes.
Then I won't.
The second sign of the rebellious phase of adolescence,
I won't let you satisfy.
Here is your paper.
This kid.
Look at you.
You really don't know how to grasp a chance when it comes.
What a good chance today,
and why don't you
talk with Siyue more.
I don't know what to talk to him.
There is nothing for us to talk about.
You are just like your dad.
You guys don't know how to socialize.
When you enter the society in the future,
you will definitely be at a disadvantage.
But take a look at Zhou Siyue,
he must be very popular.
Didn't my social life all ruined by you?
How dare you talk to your mother like that?
What are you looking for?
Where is my hat?
It is not here. Stop that.
You make such a mess. I can't tidy it up.
Go.
Then do you know where the drugstore is?
How should I know?
When I tidy everything up, I will look for your medicine.
Xianxian.
Maybe I can go with you?
No, dad. I can go myself.
I am going to the drugstore now.
Yes.
Trash.
Boring.
What are you going to do this afternoon?
Play basketball.
Dude, don't you see how my foot injured?
Can you show some mercy?
Ouch!
So now you know it hurts.
When you spoke ill about the girl just now,
didn't you feel happy?
I am not joking. It really hurts.
And
it starts to feel
more and more painful.
Perhaps
you guys can take me to the doctor's.
I happen to know a place.
Where is it?
Can you not grab me when you are hurting?
Young boy, you can't even take this pain?
Doctor, can you be more gentle?
It'll be finished right away.
I can't take it.
Miss,
are you from Shen Hai High School?
The new term is about to start.
I know what you are looking for.
This.
To help you boost your memory.
These.
Take them back.
Let your parents boil them up.
I am not here for these.
Then what do you want to buy?
I, here.
What did you bump into?
Some kind of ghost.
I don't care what you bumped into. I recommend
this to you.
I promise that if you apply it on today,
you are as good as new tomorrow.
Like you've never bumped into anything.
Come on, have a try.
You can do it!
I will pay the bill first.
Hang in there.
Siyue, I'll go with you.
Boss, the bill.
Wait a second.
What a coincidence.
Not my intention.
Why is your bump getting even bigger?
I don't want to mess around with you.
Boss, I won't buy it.
Miss, you haven't paid.
I didn't use it.
It is opened. How can I sell it to others?
How much is it?
It should be 100. But since you are student,
I will give you a 20% off.
80, then.
80?
It is only around ten Yuan in my hometown.
This is a patent of our shop.
Its cost is high.
Can I buy half of it?
Half?
Are you kidding with me, Miss?
Boss, I'll take it.
This is for the foot massage?
Is that enough?
This is?
For the drug.
Thank you.
I'll wrap it up for you.
When I get my pocket money next week, I'll give you back.
How about
treating me a meal now?
Then we are even.
OK.
What do you want to eat?
A big meal, of course.
Let's go.
Miss,
your medicine
Thanks.
You are welcome.
Take care.
Boss.
Here you are.
Give me some fish balls.
OK.
Boss.
One more marinated egg.
Please wait a moment.
Have a seat.
This is the big meal you want to eat?
This shop has been here for over a dozen years.
Its food is delicious.
About that thing today,
you don't need to think too much.
They are just like that.
Big mouth, but they don't mean harm.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Have a taste.
It is not poisonous.
It is actually tasty.
Why don't you eat?
I am not hungry. It's for you.
There are many delicious foods in Shenhai.
You can have a try if you get the chance.
Boss.
One more marinated egg.
Sure.
I don't need another one. One is enough.
This is for your bump.
Not for you to eat.
Look at your bump on your forehead.
It is becoming a horn now.
A horn? What horn?
Here you are, the egg.
I'll pay now.
OK.
I'm home.
Why did you get another one of this?
I just bought one two days ago.
The shop assistant recommended me to buy it.
The quality looks good.
And they even gave me an apron for free.
Right.
The new term is about to start the day after tomorrow.
Have you prepared everything?
Actually, I am going to school tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I got confused by so many things.
It doesn't matter. It is all the same.
The new term is about to start. Be careful not to catch a cold.
There is a big day-night temperature difference in this season.
I will fetch you a coat.
Don't bother.
I am fine.
Maybe it was just someone spoke ill of me.
Marinated egg.
Stupid marinated egg.
Tomorrow,
I'll finally become
a member of the Shen Hai High School.
But I hope
tomorrow, as the term begins,
I won't encounter
that guy.
It's really gone.
Ding Xian.
Hurry up.
Or you won't catch up with your father.
Dad, you go first.
I'll go to school by myself.
I am late.
Fine, you go by yourself.
Hurry up.
Ding Wencheng.
Be more sensible on your first day at work.
OK. I'm leaving.
Take care.
Mum, did you see my school badge?
No, where did you put it?
I...
Why are you laughing? Did you take it?
No, I didn't touch anything.
It must be you.
Ding Juncong, did you take it?
Give it back to your sister now. See how anxious she is.
I didn't take it.
Ding Xian, did you get it?
No.
Where did you put it?
You put things around casually.
I just put it on the desk.
You're going to be late.
Hurry up, Ding Xian. Just go.
Then I'll go first.
How can a girl just sit on the floor?
Mum, goodbye.
Take it slow. Be careful.
Hey.
Jiang Chen.
I've lent you my bike for the whole summer vacation.
Give it back to me this noon.
I am late for school now.
Isn't the school this way?
Don't close the gate!
Dear teachers and students,
as the zephyr greets us
and flowers bloom, in this good season,
we've welcomed a bunch of new students to our school.
Here, let's express
our welcome to them.
In the National College Entrance Examination that just came to an end,
the senior high school department of Shen Hai High School,
has again acquired...
You,
why are you late on the first day of the new term?
I got lost.
Lost?
Why didn't you lose yourself then?
Go stand at the back!
Go!
Here,
I want to express my sincere congratulation to everyone.
I know that
many students are from the main campus of this school.
And I believe
that you are all familiar with the place.
But,
high school is a brand-new start for all of you.
You are quite early.
Such bad luck.
Together with the teachers,
I wish you could build
a good study environment.
I have known you for so many years.
What's the matter with my borrowing your mirror?
No way.
Stingy.
You are the one who is stingy.
Then lend me your mirror.
I don't want to.
Fine.
After knowing each other for so many years,
our friendship finally comes to an end.
Kong Shadi.
What, Song Ziqi?
How come I can never get out of your control?
Who wants to be your deskmate?
Good for you. You are late for school on the first day.
What to be scared of?
I am not the only one who is late anyway.
Why are you looking at me?
Is there another seat for me to sit?
Where is your school badge?
You guys are so done.
You guys will surely become
the VIPs of Auntie Liu.
Auntie Liu?
Who?
You don't know?
The teacher on the opening ceremony.
Talking non-stop.
Just like my auntie.
He meddles in everything.
From your grade to your hair length.
Anything he can meddle in.
I believe you two have experienced it just now.
Good morning, students.
I am your new politics teacher.
My name is Ding Wencheng.
Mr. Ding.
Can we start the lesson with the exercises we did?
That's OK, too.
Then, everyone. Take out the paper of last year.
Let's take a look at the first question.
Stand up.
Good morning, teacher.
Sit down please.
Deng Wanwan, before we elect the class leaders officially,
you will be the acting class monitor.
Sure.
I want to add a few points.
You see how she is showing off?
-The National College Entrance Examination -After Yang Chunzi took a leave,
she has become so hyped up.
is like thousands of troops and horses crossing a single-log bridge.
From this moment on,
it's officially started.
There is no turning back.
Now that you have entered this gate,
you guys are members of Shen Hai High School already.
At least, you should live up to
the name of Shen Hai High School.
You need to prepare mentally for your study.
There is no need
to take notes about those meaningless pep talk, right?
You will learn a lot of difficult subjects.
Did anyone tell you not to peek around?
And
I have a name.
OK.
Got it.
And let me tell you,
don't try to talk to me so much from now on.
I try to talk to you?
You keep talking to me, don't you?
Don't try to cotton up.
We are about to change seats soon.
Which means, we're just temporary deskmates.
Fine.
Temporary deskmates.
About the arrangement of your seats,
it is not in a hurry yet.
The placement test is one month later.
I'll give you one month
to review
all the knowledge you've learned.
After a month, based your grade,
I will then rearrange your seats.
And,
from now on,
if I find anyone not wearing his or her school badge,
he or she can go home directly.
I will not call names.
But they know exactly whom I am talking about.
Uncle Ding.
Bocong.
I never thought you would teach our class.
Where do you sit?
There.
My poor eyesight. I didn't even see you just now.
The books are piled up.
It is natural that you couldn't to see me.
Look how much you have grown.
It feels like yesterday
that you and Xianxian running around together.
Right, Uncle Ding.
Xianxian got in our school through the exam, right?
She is in Senior One Class Three.
Xianxian has always looked up to you.
That's why she studied so hard to get into Shenhai.
Is that so? Senior One Class Three is a key class, right?
She is much better than I first entered the school.
Uncle Ding, now that you become a teacher of our school, I feel reassured.
In this case, you can
take care of Xian.
Right, like at noon,
I can have lunch with her.
I need to hurry now.
They want me to join a meeting.
OK, see you around.
Uncle Ding.
Thank you.
Just take it slow.
Siyue, let's have lunch.
Let's go, Miss Temporary Deskmate.
Are you guys going or not?
I am starving.
Go.
Wait a second.
I have something to talk to you.
The Teachers' Day is coming, right?
I want to talk about the gifts for teachers.
Right, Siyue.
Mr. Liu asked for you.
Something about joining the Olympic competition group.
Then, wait for me, guys.
Sure.
Why is Zhou Siyue not here yet?
If he doesn't come now, there will be nothing left in the canteen.
Where is he now?
I don't know.
Ding Xian, let's go for lunch.
I heard that the canteen of the senior department is quite fancy.
It is not like that in main campus of our school.
That's it. We should stop waiting for him.
Go. Let's go to have lunch.
My dad still wants to eat with me at school.
That's embarrassing.
You guys go.
Why is she running away again?
You two are to blame.
You kept picking at her in the morning.
That's why she doesn't want to eat with us.
Why has it anything to do with me?
You should ask Childe Zhou here,
what he did do to upset her.
It's none of my business.
Then explain to me.
Why did she run as soon as she saw you?
It's her legs.
You should ask her.
You can't put it that way.
Didn't you guys have, like,
a child betrothal?
What?
Don't you know?
Come, let me tell you.
That was a dark night.
You couldn't even see your own fingers.
Our Childe Zhou here...
Are you going to keep talking and talking?
No, sorry.
I am just kidding. I'll shut my mouth.
Hold on.
Xianxian.
Hello, Bocong.
You don't try to find me when you are now in Shen Hai High School?
I was afraid that you might be too busy.
Senior three.
It terrifies me when I think of it.
It's not that terrible.
How about you? What do you feel in the school?
I didn't lie to you, right?
Shen Hai High School is a stressful place.
I am not kidding about it.
Students from the main campus and those from other schools
are really different.
I don't think they are so different.
You don't need to think too much.
Just make more friends.
Makes your high school life more meaningful here.
I will try my best.
Have a taste.
Famous dish of Shen Hai High School, stewed pork with brown sauce.
Special perk for Senior Three students.
Look.
Little Monster knows that guy?
Delicious.
Who's that?
I heard about him.
Su Bocong.
Arts class of Senior Three.
He is quite a gentleman.
His grade is very good too.
He is unlike you guys.
You say this because he is handsome?
I heard that he was also from Keshan.
That's why he knows Little Monster.
Eat your meal, would you?
Hear me out.
I heard that this guy is really awesome.
His grades are excellent.
More importantly, he studies very hard.
For three years, he has never been out of Top 10.
Badass.
How good-looking that is!
Siyue, have you decided what to buy?
What? Gift for Teachers' Day.
I told you this morning.
Count me in.
Quit your nonsense.
Is she talking to you?
Maybe later.
Ding Xian, your textbooks are so new.
You don't need to go to tutor classes during vacation?
No.
You are so relaxed.
So many students in our class have already
finished learning the textbook of this term.
So what?
I forgot it all anyway.
I had no fun during the vacation.
I thought that
I could be more relaxed since I came from the main campus.
But we didn't have textbooks then, right?
You can borrow them from your seniors.
I almost forget.
You are not from the main campus, right?
You seem to be the first to come from Keshan.
It is not a surprise that you can't borrow the textbooks.
Stand up.
Good afternoon, teacher.
Sit down please.
We will talk about functions today.
Functions are actually quite simple.
It is not as complex as you think.
Let see the exercise
from the last college entrance exam.
Like this one here,
it is basically a point you must get.
Get the f(x).
How should we solve this question?
Use the method of undetermined coefficients.
How to solve it? Louder.
This is a method you have been taught.
How come some of you still don't know it?
That girl at the back,
stop looking.
Don't look around. It is you.
Stand up.
How should we solve this question?
I don't know.
What?
Zhou Siyue.
You answer it.
Read extracurricular books?
I shall see how you work this out.
The method of undetermined coefficients means
f(x)=ax²+bx+c.
Put this formula into the known equation,
we can get that a=1/2.
b=-2.
And since we know that f(0)=2,
then c=2.
Very good.
Zhou Siyue, please sit down.
You sit down too.
Did you all get it?
Yes, sir.
Interested?
No.
Stop being narcissistic.
I mean the book,
not me.
Is it not cottoning up with you, right?
Miss Temporary Deskmate?
Childish.
You've taken so many notes down.
Can you review them all?
None of your business.
This paragraph here,
the only useful part is this formula.
You just have to memorize this.
About your habit of taking every note down,
if you keep doing it,
you will be sifted out of the key class soon.
You are just above the minimum passing score.
You're ranked 45th and I am 38th.
Who are you to judge me?